<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Luarpy&#x27;s blog</title>
      <link>https://luarpy.github.io</link>
      <description></description>
      <generator>Zola</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <atom:link href="https://luarpy.github.io/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
          <title>Income counter wearable: first idea</title>
          <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>luarpy</author>
          <link>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/accounting-device-first-idea/</link>
          <guid>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/accounting-device-first-idea/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://luarpy.github.io/blog/accounting-device-first-idea/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;idea&quot;&gt;Idea&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some days ago, I found a short video on YouTube where a guy showed a gadget to get updates on the US public debt (I don&#x27;t share any opinions on it). I found the idea of wearing a pocket-sized gadget at the workplace that would show a count of the money I earn to be attractive. As a rough idea, I thought of making a similarly shaped device that shows my income per month, day or hour as time goes by. This is something I have previously thought of a device to get a better idea of my productivity or income generated per hour worked.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;img&#x2F;account_wearable&#x2F;inspiration_device.png&quot; alt=&quot;T. Massive holding the gadget&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This device is designed to represent a person&#x27;s income over a period of time, providing them with an expected idea of their income capabilities.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;concept&quot;&gt;Concept&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are the purposes I expect from this device&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track&#x2F;count my income for each hour, day, or month.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portability: The shape and size must allow it to be handheld and fit into a pocket.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Informative and simple: There is no need for complex and multipurpose data on the display.&lt;&#x2F;li&gt;
&lt;&#x2F;ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-desing&quot;&gt;First desing&lt;&#x2F;h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a handheld device, it will sit on the desktop or be held in the hand. This way, it should provide an angled visual display that is comfortable to view and hold.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;&#x2F;img&#x2F;account_wearable&#x2F;income_wearable.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; &#x2F;&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The model will be 3D printed for prototyping and used in a development environment. For this purpose, it will need to be opened several times, so it makes sense to use fasteners with inserts into the plastic.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next steps will be to create a better design and a CAD model for a first impression.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Fixing BenQ Monitor Delay</title>
          <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>luarpy</author>
          <link>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/fix-benq2780q-delay/</link>
          <guid>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/fix-benq2780q-delay/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://luarpy.github.io/blog/fix-benq2780q-delay/">&lt;p&gt;TL;DR:
El modelo BenQ EX2780Q tiene un delay de frábrica en la salida del audio por altavoces; este script escrito en Bash emite un flujo de datos sin sonido para mantener activo el trigger de entrada del audio al monitor.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Hello world</title>
          <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>luarpy</author>
          <link>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/hellow-world/</link>
          <guid>https://luarpy.github.io/blog/hellow-world/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://luarpy.github.io/blog/hellow-world/">&lt;p&gt;¡Bienvenidos al primer post de nuestro blog! Aquí comenzamos un emocionante viaje en el mundo de la ingeniería de telecomunicaciones y compartiremos nuestros intereses personales contigo. Exploraremos diversos aspectos de esta apasionante disciplina y también te llevaremos a nuestro mundo personal para conocer más sobre quiénes somos y qué nos motiva. ¡Esperamos que disfrutes de esta experiencia y que encuentres información valiosa en nuestros futuros posts! ¡Gracias por acompañarnos en este viaje!&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
